9 MONTHS EARLIER
_
캘리포니아 오클랜드
♪ It's unfortunate
that when we feel a storm ♪
너 기차 시간 늦겠다
You're going to be late
for the train.
표는 뽑아 놨어
- ♪ We can roll ourselves over ♪
- I printed your ticket.
♪ 'Cause we're uncomfortable ♪
♪ Oh, well ♪
♪ The devil makes us sin ♪
♪ But we like it
when we're spinning ♪
기차역이죠, 예?
Train station, yes?
아뇨, 공항이요
- ♪ In his grip ♪
- No, the airport.
861 기는
워싱턴 직항입니다
...Aboard flight 861,
nonstop to Washington, D.C.
현재 고도 3만 3천 피트
We are currently cruising at
an altitude of about 33,000 feet
대기 속도는
시간당 4백 마일 입니다
with an airspeed
of about 400 miles per hour.
날씨는 좋으며..
Weather looks good...
라이언 부쓰
Ryan Booth.
만나서 반갑내요
라이언 부쓰
Nice to meet you,
Ryan Booth.
워싱턴 출신이세요?
You from D.C.?
그냥 인연이 있죠
칠레에도요
Just connecting there,
on to Chile.
아.. 그럼..
Oh, well...
휴가에요?
Vacation?
국경 없는 의사요
Doctors Without Borders.
갑자기 대화가
근접하기 힘들군요
And suddenly I'm out of
my league in this conversation.
고마워요
Thanks.
그쪽은요?
What about you?
가족한테 돌아가는 길이죠
I'm heading back
to my family.
돌아간다뇨?
필리핀에 있었거든요
- Back?
- From the Philippines.
아
Oh.
우리 둘에게
마지막 자유로운 밤이네요
Last night of freedom
for us both.
그러기에 한잔
I'll drink to that.
조지아, 오거스타
_
♪ I've been silent partner,
I've been your shrink ♪
♪ I have heard you say,
"Look, misfortuous speech" ♪
유타, 실버레이크 시티
♪ But I'll have sympathy
when you get off your seat ♪
♪ Before "there's been a mess"
becomes a disease ♪
♪ I have cracked the code
on this old machine ♪
♪ 10,000 hours to be released ♪
뉴욕 시티
♪ But I've been wondering,
"Why can't you see?" ♪
♪ If the door opens up,
we go where it leads ♪
어서와요
어, 도와줘서 고맙네요
Hey, hi.
Uh, thanks for doing this.
저.. 사이먼 이예요
I'm... I'm Simon.
어, 전 맥스요
Uh, I'm Max.
어, 우리 커피 마신 거예요
Uh, we had coffee.
- 고마워요
- 네
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
어, 어디가는데요?
Uh, where you headed?
미안해요
늦었네요
Uh, sorry.
I'm late.
커피 고마워요
Thanks for the coffee.
예
Yeah.
♪ Could be yours ♪
♪ You were packing up,
but I gave you a bed ♪
♪ You would rather crash
than go straight ahead ♪
화장실 있어요?
Do you have a restroom?
♪ I wrote this years ago,
but it's finished today ♪
그게, 어, 고장났소
It's, uh, out of order.
♪ With the help of a friend
who is finished the same ♪
물건 안 사면
열쇠 못 줘요
No key
without a purchase.
♪ And I ♪
♪ I have been patient ♪
♪ But you've got to try ♪
♪ Then all of this
could be yours ♪
♪ Be yours tonight ♪
♪ Could be yours,
could be yours ♪
됐어
Okay.
그만
그럼, 전화번호나 이메일
알려주겠어?
So, can I get your number
or your E-mail?
아님... 이름이라도?
Or... your name?
너 내 타입이 아니야
You're not my type.
방금 섹스한 남자한테
하는 얘기야?
Said to the man
you just had sex with.
머, 내 타입이였으면
안했을 거거든
Well, if you were,
I wouldn't have.
너에 대해 알아가는 게
먼저였을 거야
I would have gotten
to know you first.
그럼..
Okay.
너에 대해서 다섯 가지를
말해 줄게
How about I list
five things about you
내가 맞았다는 거 알거야
to prove that I'm right,
하나라도 틀리거든
and if any of them
are false,
너가 원하는 거
뭐든 지 말해줄게
I'll tell you
whatever you want to know?
좋아
Okay.
첫째, 넌 친절해
One, you're nice.
아니야
No.
예의 바른 걸 보면
아마도 여자들이 가득한
Your good manners probably
come from having grown up
가정에서 자랐을 거야
in a house full of women.
면도하는 걸 가르쳐준
남자가 없었지
No man
taught you how to shave.
수염 자란게
방향이 엉망이야
Your stubble
grows in different directions.
둘째, 넌 결함품이야
Two, you're damaged goods.
너 결혼했었지
상당히 최근 이였을 거야
You were married,
and pretty recently, too.
그 손가락에 굳은살이
작긴해도 무르진 않거든
The callus on that finger
is small, but not soft.
셋째, 너 약삭빨라..
Three, you're slippery...
왜냐면 넌 마닐라에
갔던게 아니거든
because you weren't
in Manila.
지금 마닐라는 우기인데
네가 입은 건..
It's the rainy season in Manila,
and you're wearing...
테니스화?
Tennis shoes?
그래, 테니스화
얼룩도 없고, 새것도 아니고
Right, tennis shoes,
which are spotless, but not new,
그게, 넷째, 네가 사실
북동쪽에서 왔다면
which, four, you would have
called "sneakers"
스니커즈라고 했겠지
if you really were
from the Northeast,
그 반대로..
서부해안?
as opposed to...
the West Coast?
로스앤젤리스..
Los Angeles...
호쏜.. 이 정확하겠네
Hawthorne, to be exact.
그래서, 다섯째
도대체 믿을 수가 없잖아
Which makes you, five,
pretty damn untrustworthy,
내가 흥분될만한 것을
찾아 차에 타서는
and while I find that
enough of a turn-on
우리가 그거를 하긴 했지만
to get into this car
and do what we just did,
길게 보자면
확실히 내 타입은 아니야
in the long run,
definitely not my type.
호쏜?
Hawthorne?
호쏜 등록증
_
너 누구야?
Who are you?
지금으로썬
평생 모를걸
Guess you'll
never know now.
나는 국내외 모든 적들에 맞서
I solemnly swear
to support and defend
미 합중국 헌법을 받들며
수호하겠음을
the constitution of the United
States against all enemies,
엄숙히 맹세합니다
foreign and domestic.
진실된 믿음과 충성을
함께 간직하겠습니다
I will bear true faith
and allegiance to the same.
나는 어떠한 의구심도 없이
I take this obligation freely,
기꺼이 선택한 의무를
져버리지 않을 것이며
without any reservation
or purpose of evasion
내가 속하게
되는 곳에서의 의무를
and will well and faithfully
discharge
충실히 이행하고
떠나겠습니다...
the duties of the office
of which I am about to enter...
신이시여 돌봐 주소서
So help me God.
콴티코 FBI 학교에
온것을 환영한다
Welcome to the FBI Academy
at Quantico.
난 특수요원
리암 오코너다
I'm Special Agent
Liam O'Connor.
축하한다
Congratulations.
다들 여기까지 왔다
You made it in.
이제 여러분이
살아남을 지 봐야죠
Now let's see
if you can survive.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
호칭이 좀 안맞을 수 있습니다
재수정 없습니다
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
뉴욕, 그랜드 센트럴 역
_
여기! 여기요!
Hey! Over here!
FBI다!
움직이지 마!
FBI! Don't move!
양손 내가 볼 수 있게하고!
Keep your hands
where I can see them!
저도 FBI예요!
여기 신분증이..
I'm FBI!
I have my crede...
- 움직이지 말랬지!
- 알았어요
- I said, "Don't move"!
- Okay.
움직이려는
생각조차 하지마!
Don't you even think
about moving!
쏘지마!
Hold your fire!
아, 알겠어요
Okay, okay.
자켓 주머니요
Jacket pocket.
여긴 위험해
This area's not safe.
나랑 같이 가지
Come with me.
이나라의 안위가
The state of this country
이처럼 위태로운 때는
없었습니다
is the most precarious
it has ever been.
위협이 전에 없이
많아진 것 뿐만 아니라
DAY ONE 9:00 AM - OT
Not only are there more threats
than ever before,
대부분의 위협이
but the majority
of those threats
알려진 단체나 극단주의자들에게서
오는 것이 아니라
don't come
from known organizations
우리 뒷마당에서...
여러분이 같이 자라온 이웃이나
or extremist groups,
but our own backyard...
여러분이 하룻밤 같이 지낸 상대나
어쩌면 가족 중에서
a neighbor you grew up next to,
a one-night stand you had,
나온다는 것입니다
perhaps even a family member.
여러분은 그러한 위협에서 여러분의 나라를
지키고자 여기 응시했습니다
You applied here to protect
your country from those threats.
여러분의 이상이나
여러분의 시험 점수가
And while your ideals
and your test scores
여러분을 이곳으로
오게 했지만
might have gotten you here,
여기에 머물기에는
그것으로 부족합니다
they will not be enough
to keep you here.
FBI 훈련소는
극도로 힘든 신병 교육대이며
The FBI Academy
is the toughest boot camp,
하나로 뭉쳐진
단단한 대학원입니다
hardest grad school
rolled into one.
대학교 같은게 아닙니다
It is not college.
사느냐 죽느냐죠
It is life and death.
참 따뜻한 분이네
She's so warm.
- 각 신병 학급이나..
- 그럴리가
- Every class of New Agent Trainees,
- She can't be.
- NAT 들은..
- 저분이 대장인데
- or NATs...
- She's the boss.
- ..확실히 그러한..
- 그게 뭐?
- ...to make sure that only those...
- So what?
- 기관의 졸업 요건을 갖춘..
- 우리가 여기서 잘하면
- ...who meet bureau standards graduate.
- We do really well here,
아주 잘된 경우에 말야
best-case scenario,
무성별의, 심장도 없고
거들먹거리는 로봇이 되는거야?
end up a sexless, heartless,
pontificating robot?
힐러리 밑에서 일하겠지
Worked for Hillary.
너희는 임시 신분증과
제복, 빨간 손잡이 권총을
You'll receive
temporary credentials,
지급 받게 될 것이다
uniforms,
and a red-handled gun.
언제나 제복을 입고
언제나 신분증을 지참하고
Always wear the uniform,
always have your credentials,
언제나 빨간 권총을 휴대한다
always carry
the red-handle.
그래야만 너희가
방문객이나 DEA 훈련병
That way, you're identifiable
to us as a New Agent Trainee,
이웃인 해병도 아닌
신입 요원 훈련병으로
or NAT, and not visiting law
enforcement, a D.E.A. trainee,
구분된다
or a neighboring marine.
권총은 표적 훈련시
Guns can be rented
for target practice
빨간 권총을 맡기고
대여된다
by leaving your red-handle.
권총을 반납하면
빨간 권총을 돌려받는다
Return your gun,
recover your red-handle.
나 꼭 틸다 스윈턴 처럼
나왔네
I look like Tilda Swinton.
난 사이먼이야
어, 처음 만나네
I'm Simon.
Uh, we haven't met yet.
그래
Okay.
중성적 제복
Gender-neutral uniforms.
평등의 승리려나?
A win for equality?
갈등되네
I'm conflicted.
알렉스 페리쉬 야
Alex Parrish.
쉘비 와이엇
Shelby Wyatt.
- 만나서 반가워
- 그래, 나도
- Good to meet you.
- Yeah, you too.
이건 어디다 써?
What's this for?
쏘지도 못하잖아
It doesn't even shoot.
그렇게 너 자신을
It's so you get used
권총을 휴대하는 무게에
익숙하게 하는거지
to having the weight
of a gun on your person.
진짜 총 쏴 본적 있어?
You ever shot
a real one before?
난 양궁 선수였지
I was
a competitive archer.
같은 건 아니잖아
That's not the same thing.
2012년 올림픽 심판들은
꽤나 좋게 봐주던데
The Olympic judges seemed
pretty impressed in 2012.
난.. 회계사였어
I-I used to be a C.P.A.
취미라곤 이거 하나였지
This was my only hobby.
잘됐네
Good.
해병대 커피는
엿 같았거든
Coffee sucked
in the Marines.
나이 30에
또다시 여름캠프라니
30 years old,
and I am back at summer camp.
내가 도와줄게
Let me help.
내가 침대 정리는 잘하거든
I make
mean hospital corners.
고마워
Thank you.
너 옷 속에다가
파자마 입은 거야?
You were wearing pajamas
under your clothes?
잠깐 있어봐
Wait. Hold up.
너 "엘더 에릭"이지?
Are you "Elder Eric"?
이럴수가!
No way!
이봐
Hey.
저기서도 알아?
Do they know?
당연하지
날 선발했는데
Of course.
They recruited me.
왜?
Why?
그야, 몰몬교인은 권위를 존중하고
술이나 약에 손대지 않고
Well, mormons respect authority,
don't drink or take drugs,
해외에서 많은 시간을
보내서
spend time
in foreign countries,
여러 언어를
할 수 있으니까
and they speak
several languages.
너한테는 하나도
적용되지 않는 것 같은데?
I'm assuming none of that
applies to you?
- 어디서 선교했어?
- 말라위(동남아프리카)
- Your mission?
- Malawi.
늘 가보고 싶었는데
_
놀라운 민족의 나라지
조지아엔 가본 적 없는데
I've never been
to Georgia.
라이언 부쓰
만나서 반가워
Ryan Booth.
Nice to meet you.
6시간 전에 네 차에서
우리 섹스했잖아
We had sex in your car
six hours ago.
사람들이 모르기를
바랬을 거라고 생각했는데
I didn't think you'd want
everyone to know that.
뭐 어때?
Why not?
우리 늦겠다
We're gonna
be late.
니마 여자앤
독방 쓰는거야?
That Nimah girl
got a single?
그래, 어
독실한 무슬림 여자는
Yeah,
uh, devout Muslim women
노출된 모습을 남자들에게
보이면 안된다나봐
aren't supposed to be seen
uncovered by men.
그러니까 저기다 넣어버리면
그런일 없을 거잖아
They probably put her in there
so it doesn't happen.
그래, 그렇지
Yeah, I know.
니마?
Nimah?
그게 말야, 너도
첫 모임 놓치고 싶지 않..
I tell you, you don't want
to miss your first big...
아! 미.. 미안해
Oh! I'm... I'm sorry.
모.. 모두한테 그 얘기 하고
다니고 있었거든
I-I was just telling everyone
about this same thing.
어, 난 게이야, 그러니..
Uh, I'm gay, so...
그렇다고 뭐가 달라져?
And that makes
a difference?
아니
Nope.
나가
Get out.
이 서류들 속에
FBI가 너희 지원 과정에서 모은
1:00 PM - THE ASSIGNMENT
Inside these folders
is every piece of information
모든 정보들이 들어있다..
the FBI gathered on you during
your application process...
한가지 정보가 수정되있지
with one item redacted.
정보가 CIA의 게임이라면
수사가 우리의 게임이다
If intelligence is the CIA's
game, investigation is ours.
어떻게 나보다 빨리왔어?
How'd you beat me?
누군가의 신분이 도난당하거나
Someone's identity is stolen,
- 연쇄살인마가 나타나거나..
- 엘리베이터
- a serial killer strikes...
- The elevator.
..폭탄이 터지거나..
...a bomb goes off...
만약 단서가 없다고 하더라도
언제나 실마리는 있다
Even if there are no leads,
there are always clues.
아주 작은 세부사항이
큰 차이를 만들어낸다
The smallest detail
can make a huge difference.
너희는 동료 훈련병들을
하나 찍어서
So you are going to pick
a fellow trainee,
24시간 안에
그들 이야기 속에서
figure out the missing piece
of their story
빠진 조각을 찾아낸다
못하면 탈락이다
in the next 24 hours,
or you're out.
행운을 빈다
Godspeed.
내꺼 바로 저깄어
의사양반
I'm right there, "doctor."
왜그래
난 이미 너 파악했다고
Please.
I've already figured you out.
베데스타에 우리 아버지가
들으면 아주 좋아하실거야
Oh, my dad in Bethesda
will be so happy to hear that.
내가 원하던거 찾았네
Got what I wanted.
네 건 누가 벌써
가져가버렸나보네
It looks like
somebody already got yours.
어-어-어
자기거 가져가면 안되지
Unh-unh-unh.
You can't take your own.
조셉 스미스
Joseph Smith.
너 마누라가 몇이나
되는지 함 봐야지
I want to see
how many wives you have.
몇 시간 전 폴발로
뉴욕 그랜드 센트럴역이
It was only a few hours
ago that an explosion
흔들렸습니다
rocked Grand Central Terminal
in New York City,
그곳에서 멀지 않은
월도프 아스토리아 호텔에서
not far from where the
Democratic National Convention
민주당 전당대회가
진행되고 있었죠
was just getting under way
at the Waldorf Astoria.
합동 테러 대책반에
지메네즈 부장이야
ASAC Jimenez,
Joint Terrorism Task Force.
아직 우리도 무슨 일이 있었는지
정보를 모으고 있지
We're still piecing together
what happened here,
자네 도움이 정말로
필요하네
but we could really
use your help.
저요? 왜요?
Mine? Why?
저는 요원이 된지
몇달밖에 안됐다고요
I've only been an agent
for a few months.
전 전당대회
외곽 경비 중이였고요
I was on perimeter detail
at the Convention.
그리고, 우리 사람들
구해야 하지 않나요? 그러니까..
And shouldn't we
be helping people? I mean...
아니야, 현장에는
요원들과 지역 지원이 있고
No. We've got agents
and local L.E. on the ground,
포트 헤밀턴에서
군지원도 올거야
military personnel
coming in from Fort Hamilton.
자넨 여기서
더 유용하네
You're more useful
to us here.
자넨 폭발 현장 가장 가까운데서
발견된 생존자야
You're the closest survivor
we've found to the blast site.
그러기에
최고의 증인이 되는거지
That makes you
our best witness.
하지만 전 기억나는게 전혀..
But I don't remember
anything. I...
자네 생각보다는
더 많은 걸 기억할 거야
You might remember
more than you think.
따라오게
Follow me.
폭발 바로 직전에
정보를 하나 입수했었지
We got a tip
right before the explosion.
- 너무 늦기는 했지만..
- 그게 뭐죠?
- Too late to stop, but...
- What was it?
우리 요원들 중 한명에 의한
내부소행이라는 거였어
That it was an inside job
by one of our own agents.
예?
말도 안되요
What?
That's crazy.
하지만, 정보는 그보다
더 구체적이였어
But it was more specific
than that.
이 사람들
얼마나 잘 알고 있나?
How well
do you know these people?
이해가 안되는데요
I don't understand.
자네가 저들을
지켜봤다는 거 아네
We know
you researched them.
그치, 6개월이나
저들과 같이 살았었지
Hell, you lived together
for six months.
자네가 파악한 사실을
기억해줘야 겠어
We need you to remember
what you found.
잠깐만요
지금 저들 중 한 명이
Wait. Are you telling me
you think
테러리스트라는
말씀이세요?
one of these people
is a terrorist?
그뿐만 아니라
콴티코에 들어갈 때 이미
Not only that, we're pretty sure
they already were a terrorist
테러리스트였다고
확신하네
when they got to Quantico.
그게 정보 내용이야
That's what the tip was.
누군지 밝혀내는데
자네 도움이 필요하네
We need your help
to figure out who they are
그래야 또다른 공격을
막을 수가 있네
so we can stop them
before they strike again.
내 부하들이
폭탄 장비를 들여왔으니
My guys are getting
the bomb techs in
더 이상 놀랄 일은
없도록 할 겁니다
so we can make sure
there aren't more surprises.
교량과 터널은 모두 막아서
누구도 출입이 불가합니다
Bridges and tunnels
are closed... no one in or out.
도시는 911 때 만큼이나
단단하게 봉쇄됐습니다
City's on lockdown,
tight as 9/11.
- 좋아요. 계속 알려주세요
- 그러죠
- Okay, keep me posted.
- Copy that.
그럼..
So...
둘쨋날
무슨 일이 있었지?
day two.
What happened?
둘쨋날
오전 6시 - 기상
♪ You dragged me to the doctor,
and you didn't tell me why ♪
♪ A 9-year-old in headphones
raising hands, raising hell ♪
♪ Raise 'em high ♪
♪ Oh, you better
raise 'em high ♪
♪ I don't want
to go to church no more ♪
♪ I don't want to go to school ♪
♪ Got Jesus on the dashboard ♪
♪ And the devil's sitting
in a pew right next to you ♪
눈을 뗄 술 없는
내가 싫다
I hate
that I can't stop looking.
난 아닌데
- ♪ Oh, he's right next to you ♪
- I don't.
저기!
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- Hey!
어제도 그 옷 입지 않았어?
Didn't you wear that
yesterday?
술집에서 잔거야?
Fall asleep at a bar?
네가 그렇게나 관심을
가지는지 몰랐는데
I didn't realize you were
paying such close attention.
제대로 하라고
얘기 했지
I told you
to pull it together.
그래서 해보겠다고
얘기 했지
And I told you I'd try.
기억해, 난 이제는
네 동료도, 여자친구도 아니야
Remember, I'm not your partner
or your girlfriend anymore,
거기다 친구도 아니지
and I'm not your friend.
- 네 상관이라고
- 흠
- I'm your boss.
- Hmm.
그보다는 교도소장에
가까운 것 같은데..
You feel
a little more like a warden...
그게 그럴게 여기가 꼭
교도소 같거든
which makes sense, 'cause
this place feels like prison.
문제를 일으킨건 너자신이야
리암, 내가 아니라고
You got yourself into trouble,
Liam, not me.
여기서 널 보고싶지는
않았었어
This is the last place
I wanted to see you.
그럼 왜 데려온건데?
Then why bring me here?
그래야 네가 연금하고
자존심을 유지하고
So you could keep
your pension and your pride
품위있는 모습으로
시간을 보낼 수 있으니까
and count down the clock
with some semblance of dignity.
음, 너처럼
Mm. Like you are.
난 그런게 아니지
That's not
what I'm doing.
뭐?
Oh?
어떤 여성도 콴티코에서
No woman
has gotten higher
부원장 이상으로
올라간 적이 없었지
than the Assistant Director
of Quantico.
단 한명도
No woman.
내가 뭘 하는지는
상관없어
It doesn't matter
what I do.
모집 숫자도 지금까지
최고이면서도
Recruitment numbers are the
largest that they've ever been,
난 여기 있잖아
and I'm still here.
네가 깨기 전까지는
천정은 그저 유리일 뿐이지
The ceiling's only glass
till you break it.
그게 정확히 남자라면
할 만한 말이지
That's exactly the kind of thing
that only a man would say.
이 일하면서
난 가족을 잃었어
I lost my family
to this job.
나도 그래
So did I.
그래, 그치만 내가
그때문에 죽도록 술마시는거
Yeah, but you don't see me
drinking myself to death
본적은 없지, 있어?
over it, do you?
네 방식으로 안된다고
그냥 포기하다니
Just giving up
'cause it didn't go your way.
너 가라앉는데
내가 구해줬잖아
I saved you from drowning.
하지만, 곧바로 다시
널 집어던질 수도 있어
I could just as soon
toss you back in.
잊지말라고, 알았지?
Don't forget that, okay?
체력훈련, 무기
방어 전술...
P.T., firearms,
defensive tactics...
이 숙제 할만한 시간이 없잖아
오전 9시 - 훈련
there's no time
for this assignment.
그래
나도 밤에나 시작했어
Yeah,
I started last night.
난 벌써 끝냈는데
사이먼은 쉽더라고
I'm already done.
Simon's easy.
내가 솔직함을 선호하지
I prefer honest.
숨길게 전혀 없거든
I have nothing to hide.
저기, 음..
Hey, um...
어쨌든, 어제 말야..
by the way,
about yesterday...
내가 문 열었을 때?
when I opened the door?
어, 신경쓰지마
괜찮아
Oh, don't worry about it.
It's fine.
뭐 하나 물어봐도 될까?
음..
May I ask a question?
Um...
그.. 그게 눈에 띄던데
어쩔땐 히잡 핀을
I-I noticed that sometimes
you... you pin your hijab
왼쪽에 하는데
어쩔 때는 오른 쪽에 하더라고
to the left
and sometimes to the right.
내가 미처 몰랐던
문화적 특성이 있는거야
Is there a cultural significance
I'm unaware of,
아님 그냥 네가 핀을
잡는대로 하는거야?
or is it just the way you hold
the pin when you clasp it?
네가 양손잡이인건
알거든
I noticed
you're ambidextrous.
맞아
Yes.
안녕들 한가
Good morning.
안녕하십니까
- Morning, sir.
- Morning.
난 특수요원
피트 페어맨이다
I'm Special Agent Pete Fairman.
내가 너희들 첫번째
자격시험을 주관할 것이다
And I'll be conducting
your first qualification tests.
각자에 대한 조사가
제대로 시작한 건 언제지?
When did the investigation
of each other start in earnest?
훈련들 사이에요
점심 때, 사격장에서..
In between activities, during
lunch, at the shooting range...
예, 그 쪽 고객일로
전화 했는데요. 쉡리 와이어트요
Yes, I'm calling about
your client, Shelby Wyatt.
쉘비 와이어트
Shelby Wyatt.
와이어트 양의 변호사 말로는
그쪽에서 가문 재산을 관리하신다고요
♪ You saw me slipping on my blind side ♪
회계사 말로는 와이어트가 재산의 대부분은
2001년까지 그쪽 은행에 있었더군요
♪ I'm feeling lost, feeling tongue-tied ♪
♪ And now I'm frozen
in your headlights ♪
♪ Deep in the haze of your love high ♪
그만!
Time!
아주 인상적이군
아민 훈련병
Very impressive,
Trainee Amin.
아주 인상적이야
- ♪ I used to soar on the live wire ♪
- Very impressive.
저게 오는 거 봤는데
I saw that one coming.
♪ I'm coming down
from your supply ♪
쟤 무시하지 말라고
Don't discount her.
이쪽이 전문 기술이
아니라서 그래
- ♪ And I don't know if you can ♪
- This just isn't in her skill set.
그럼 뭔데?
- ♪ Make right ♪
- What is?
♪ I can't take it ♪
♪ From the day
I saw my heart start breaking ♪
♪ No one saved me ♪
아버님이랑 사냥 다니면서
유명해졌지
She got famous
hunting with her dad.
American sniper.
친구가 2천명?
2,000 friends?
전부 별 5개 주는건
도대체 누구야?
Who gives everything
five stars?
왜 여기 올라온 영화가
"City Slickers" 하나 뿐이냐고?
Why is the only movie on here
"City Slickers"?
에릭 인스타그램 말야..
뭐. 그냥.. 유행어들 뿐이네
Eric's Instagram, it's...
it's... it's just memes.
다시 연락주셔서
감사합니다
Thank you
for getting back to me.
페리쉬 양이 구직 추천인에
당신을 올려두었더군요
Ms. Parrish had you listed
as a reference for the position,
그래서 제가..
and I was hoping...
제가..
I was...
죄송해요
Sorry.
있잖아요
약간의 정보를 좀..
I was hoping maybe you could,
you know...
얻을 수 있을까 합니다
- ♪ I can't take it ♪
- ...give me a little information
페리쉬 양이
어떤 직원이였는지 말이죠
on what type of employee
she was.
♪ I saw my heart start breaking ♪
잡았다
- ♪ No one saved me ♪
- Gotcha.
♪ I should have known ♪
♪ Known, known ♪
♪ No, no, no, no ♪
♪ Watch it ♪
내가 하루종일
케일럽을 들여다 봤는데
Well, I have looked
into Caleb all day.
완전 금동이라니까
He is a total golden boy.
그거 알아? 감독이 직접
걔 추천서 써준거?
You know the Director himself
wrote his recommendation?
어이
Hey.
얘 서류에서
수정된 사항이라곤
The only thing they could
have redacted about him
분명 복근에 스프레이
뿌린게 다일 거야
is where he gets
his abs sprayed on.
분명 뭔가
숨기고 있을거야
He must be hiding
something.
아, 그렇지
Oh, right.
너희 거기 없었구나
You guys
weren't there.
19... 20...
15...
담배 피거든
I smoke.
제 총에 무슨 문제가
있는 것 같습니다
I think there's
something wrong with my gun.
젠장!
Damn it!
우리 금동이가 어쩜
금도금 일지도 몰라
So it looks like Golden Boy
might only be gold-plated.
그래서, 걔가 자기 외모 믿고
So, what, did he think
설렁설렁 해도 된다고
생각한다는 거야?
he could just coast through
on his looks?
아마도
Probably.
나 설렁설렁 하지 않거든
테일러 스위프트
I'm not coasting on anything,
Taylor Swift.
내가 패커에 대해 찾은 걸
발표할 때 보면 알게 될 거야
You'll see when I present
what I just found on Packer.
이봐, 말라위와 시간 차이는?
Hey, what's the time difference
to Malawi?
일곱 시간
Seven hours.
왜?
Why?
그 다음에는?
And then what happened?
수업시간이였는데요
It was time for class.
우리 총을 반납 했고요
We returned our guns.
무슨 일이 있었는지는
이미 아시잖아요
You already know
what happened next.
좋아 그래. 뭘 찾았나본데
나도 좀 알지
All right, so, you found
something, I take it?
아, 내가 생각했던 것보다
훨씬 더한 거더라고
Oh, so much better
than I expected, too.
알았어, 나도 물었다고
Okay. I'll bite.
우, 롬니, 진정하라고
Whoa, Romney, relax.
다른 애들처럼 너도
놀래보고 싶지 않아?
Don't you want to be surprised
like everyone else?
그래서 좀 묻자..
배경조사는 어떻게 통과한 거야?
Though I got to ask... how'd
you pass a background check?
거짓말이군
You're lying.
아무 것도 없네
There's nothing.
이봐
그만하라고, 하스
Hey.
Lay off him, Haas.
저기. 그냥 얘가
제대로 준비됐는지..
Hey, I just want him
to be prepared...
자기가 한건
자기가 알잖아
'cause he knows
what he did.
넌 솔트레이크에
계속 있었어야지, 꼬마야
You should have stayed
in Salt Lake, boy.
저기, 저렇게 그냥 두면 안돼
Hey, don't let him
get to you.
그래, 쟤가 뭘 알아냈던지
Yeah,
and whatever he's found,
FBI는 벌써 다
알고 있어, 그찮아?
the FBI already knew
about it, right?
가자
Come on.
수사는 끝났다
오후 3시 - 심문
The investigation is over.
이제 심문으로
넘어갈 시간이다..
Now it's time to move on...
to the interview.
자네들 각자 찾아낸
사실이 있겠지
Each of you
has a fact you've found,
진실이라고 믿는
정보의 조각 말이다
a piece of information
you believe to be true,
하지만, 그것은 용의자에게서
확인을 받아야 한다
but you need confirmation
from your suspect.
"수사와 심문"은..
"Investigation and interview"...
FBI의
"빵과 버터"이다..
the bread and butter
of the FBI...
이 둘에서 뛰어나지 못하면
너희는 절대 해낼 수 없다
and if you can't excel at both,
you'll never make it through.
그리고 현실적으로는
거짓말 탐지기가
And while in the real world,
a polygraph
법원에서 받아들여지지
않을지더라도
might be inadmissible
in a court of law,
난 무엇을 알아내는데
훌륭한 도구라는 걸 알게됐다
I find it
a great tool to learn by.
"예" "아니요" 질문에만
집중하도록 하고
Stick to
"yes" or "no" questions,
얼마나 얻어낼 수 있는지
보도록 하지
and let's see how far you get.
그래, 누가 먼저였지?
So, who went first?
심문 1 - 쉘비 와이어트
_
망막 카메라는
어디에 쓰는 거죠?
What's
the Retina camera for?
눈동자의 움직이나 팽창은
간혹 결정적 증거가 되지
Eye movement and dilation
are often dead giveaways.
사이먼, 시작하게
Simon, you can begin.
조지아에서 자랐나?
You grew up in Georgia?
물론, 예
I sure did, yes.
가족과 함께?
With your family?
예
Yes.
독자인가?
Are you an only child?
예
Yes.
어, 그게
이복 자매가 있어
Uh, well,
I-I have a half-sister.
나보다 10살 많은데
잘 알지는 못해
She's 10 years older, though.
I barely know her.
진정해
괜찮으니까
Stay calm.
It's okay.
부모님은 어떠셔?
What about your parents?
부모님이 뭐?
What about them?
두분 다 살아계셔?
Are they still alive?
아니
No.
아니야
They are not.
어떻게 돌아가셨지?
How did they die?
이거 "예" "아니요" 질문이
아닌데
That's not
a "yes" or "no" question.
두분 같이 돌아가셨어?
Did they die together?
예
Yes.
살해당하셨나?
Were they killed?
예
Yes.
내가 16살 때
When I was 16.
네가 가지고 다니는
금속 조각은 뭐지?
What's the piece of metal
you carry with you?
질문 다시
Rephrase.
그 금속 조각은
비행기에서 나온거지?
Is that piece of metal
part of a plane?
예
Yes.
부모님이 타고 계셨던
비행기지?
The plane
your parents were on?
예
Yes.
9월 11일
On 9/11.
내가 여기 있는 이유지
That's why I'm here.
잘했다, 사이먼
Well done, Simon.
잘했어
Well done.
다음은 누구였지?
Who went next?
넌 게이야
You're gay.
예, 그건 비밀도 아닌데
Yes, but that is not a secret.
네 서류에는 없는거지
It wasn't in your file.
그건 차별이 되기 때문이지
Because that would be
discrimination.
그러면 내가 너보고
동정이라고 한다면
And would it be
discrimination
그것도 차별이
되는 건가?
if it had said
you were a virgin?
니마가 이겼네!
Nimah for the win!
잠깐
저거 거짓말이잖아, 그치?
Wait.
That's a lie, right?
거짓말 탐지기에 의하면
아니지
Not according
to the polygraph.
내가 최근 네 남자친구들
4명하고 얘기해 봤는데
Because when I spoke
to your last four boyfriends,
다들 그렇게 말하더군
that's what they said.
니마, 그건
사이먼의 비밀이 아닌데
Nimah, that isn't
Simon's secret.
그럴수도 있잖아요
It should have been.
자네 이 과제를 진지하게
생각하지 않은 게 분명하군
Clearly you didn't take
the assignment seriously.
끝내게
You're done.
사이먼 아셔
넌 독실한 시온파 가정 출신의
Simon Asher,
you are a Conservative Jew
보수적인 유태인이야
from
a staunch Zionist family,
헌데 4년 전
넌 팔레이스타인 들과 함께 살려고
yet four years ago,
you traveled to Gaza
가자 지구로 여행을 갔지
to live
with the Palestinians,
그리고 오늘까지
아무한테도 얘기한 적 없어
and to this day,
you never told anyone.
미안, 깜박했네..
예, 아니요?
Sorry. I forgot...
yes or no?
예
Yes.
걔가 가자 지구로 간건
더 잘 알기 위해서였다고요
He only went to Gaza because
he wanted to be better informed.
그야, 녀석이 너한테
그렇게 말한거지
Well, that's
what he told you.
진짜 이유는 알잖아
We know the real reason.
- 자넨 어떤가?
- 제가 뭐가요?
- What about you?
- What about me?
아, 거짓말 탐지기
필요 없어요
Oh, I don't need
the polygraph.
알렉스는 거짓말
안 할테니까요
Alex won't lie.
그렇지, 알렉스?
Right, Alex?
- 괜찮아요
- 좋아
- That's fine.
- Good.
- 봤나, 아주 좋아
- 그래, 그렇지
- See, that's good.
- Yes, that's right.
방금 알렉스를 자신을
믿을 수 있도록 만든 거야
He's making her feel
like she can trust him.
어쨌거나, 난 믿으면 안돼
준비나 잘 하라고
You can't trust me, by the way,
just so you're prepared.
너하고 나, 내 차에서
You and me, in my car.
그런거 자주해?
You do that often?
내가 원하는 만큼
자주는 아니야
Not as often as I'd like.
음
Mm.
네가 그러는 거
말야 혹시나
Do you think
perhaps you do it
네 인생에서 남자들과의
해결되지 않는 문제들 때문인거야?
because of unresolved issues
with men in your life?
내 인생에
남자가 많지 않거든
I don't have many men
in my life,
그러니 남자들과
문제가 있는게
so I don't know
how it'd be possible
가능이나 한지 모르겠네
to have any issues
with them.
음, 그럼 다른 사람과
관계를 맺는 것에 대한
Mm. So you don't think
that a person's inability
무능력함이
사람들의 과거에서
to connect
with somebody else
비롯된다고
생각하진 않는 건가?
comes from something
in their past?
네가 말해 보시지?
Why don't you tell me?
너희 아버지
Your father.
우리 아버지 어떤게?
What about my father?
그게, 찾기 힘드신
분이더군
Well, he's a hard man
to find.
제 페이스북 페이지에
그분 사진이 한장도 없었고
You don't have any pictures
of him on your Facebook page.
둘이 함께 있던 사진들엔
태그를 모두 떼버렸지
You untagged any photos
of the two of you together.
사실은
아버지가 돌아가셨을 때
In fact,
when he passed away,
넌 그분을 전혀
언급하지 않았었지
you didn't mention him
at all.
혼자서만
슬퍼하는 쪽이야
I prefer to grieve
in private.
나도 동의하지..
I would agree...
네가 정말로
슬퍼했던 거라면 말야
if you'd
actually been grieving.
내가 물어볼까
아님 네가 그냥 말해줄래
I can ask,
or you can just tell me.
어느쪽이든 기분이
나아질 거야
Whatever makes you
feel better.
나가요!
Get out!
아니! 네가 나가!
No! You get out!
왜요?
Why?
당신 생각이나 해봤어?
Do you ever think
of that?!
아이도 있잖아!
You have kids!
저리가라, 얘야
Stay away, sweetie.
아빠, 안돼!
Daddy, no!
아빠 말대로 해, 알렉스
위험해
Do what he says, Alex.
It's not safe.
아빠 또 술 마셨어
He's drunk again.
애한테 거짓말 마!
Don't lie to her!
애한테 사실을 말해!
한번이라도, 시타!
Tell her the truth!
For once, Sita!
- 아빠, 그만해!
- 젠장 평생 한번이라도!
- Daddy, stop!
- For once in your damn life!
아빠, 제발 총 내려!
제발요!
Daddy, please put
the gun down! Please!
당신의 대한 진실?
The truth about you?
아빠, 안돼!
Daddy, no!
[screams]
누구 좀 불러, 알렉스!
Get help, Alex!
제발, 도와줘!
Please, help!
제발!
Please!
그래서 어머니가
아버지를 쐈지..
So your mother shot him...
정당방위였어?
In self-defense?
그래, 맞아
Yes, that's right.
그만해도 좋다, 라이언
You can stop now, Ryan.
그거 감동적이네요
That was emotional.
근데, 알렉스의 비밀은
에릭에 비하면 별거 아니네요
But her secret's
got nothing on Eric's.
오코너 특수 요원님
다음은 저희가 하죠?
S.A. O'Connor,
can we go next?
펙커, 넌 추락하는 거야
Packer, you're going down.
엘더 에릭
네 비밀을 안다고
Elder Eric,
I know your secret.
어서와
Come on in.
털어 놓을 준비 됐어
엘더 에릭?
You ready to come clean,
Elder Eric?
총 내려놔
Put the gun down.
넌 말 못해
You won't tell.
말하게 두진 않겠어!
I won't let you!
보세요
제가 계속 얘기하다보면
Look, you seem to think
that if I keep talking,
무슨 마술같은 기억이
풀리면서
I'll unlock
some magic memory
당신이 들은 얘기를 뒷받침 해
줄 거라고 생각하시나 본데요
to support whatever it is
that you've been told, but...
다른 훈련병들한테
가서 얘기해 보셔야 겠거든요
Maybe you should talk
to the other trainees.
난 지금 자네랑 얘기 중이야
I'm talking to you.
근데 그게
시간 낭비라니까요!
But we're wasting time
in here!
밖에 우리 도움이 필요한 사람들이
있잖아요. 다치고..
There are people out there who
are hurt, who need our help...
그리고 다음엔?
What happened next?
에릭..
Eric...
에릭, 총 내려 놓으라고
Eric, put the gun down.
왜 그걸 찾아봐야
한건데, 어?
Why'd you have to go looking,
man?
왜 그냥 가만두지 않았냐고?
Why couldn't you just leave it alone?!
- 내가 뻥카친거야
- 문 열어, 에릭!
- I was bluffing.
- Open the door, Eric!
괜찮아?
나 아무것도 못 찾았거든
All right?
I didn't find anything.
찾아는 봤는데..
근데 전혀 안나오더라고
I looked. I did.
But... but nothing turned up.
에릭, 문열라고!
Eric, open the door!
널 어떻게 믿어!
I don't believe you!
아무것도 못 찾았다고
맹세해!
I didn't find anything,
I swear!
문 열어!
Open the door!
됐지? 난 그냥..
그런 척 해본 거라고
Okay? I was just...
I was just pretending.
뭐 아는 것 처럼 하면
I thought that if I pretended
- 뭔가 나올 까 해서..
- 거짓말 하지마..
- to find something...
- You're lying.
..어슬렁 거리고 짜증나게
군건데, 네가..
...and riled you up with it,
you'd just...
네가 혹시나 실수로
털어놓을까 해서
you'd let
your secret slip.
네가..
네가 그래야 내가..
And I...
and I needed you to.
총 내려, 에릭!
총 내려!
Put the gun down, Eric!
Put the gun down!
그게 시험에
전부 떨어져서
'Cause after failing
all those tests,
이것도 떨어지면
나 쫓겨난단 말이야
if I failed this,
they'd send me home.
그니까..
제발 총 좀..
Just...
just put the gun...
제발 총 좀
치워 달라고
Please put
the gun away, man.
- 거짓말이지. 너 못 믿어
- 제발 좀!
- You're a liar. I don't believe you.
- Just come on!
모두한테 말할 거잖아!
다들 알게 될거야!
You'll tell everybody!
Everyone will know!
에릭, 에릭, 알았다고
그냥 총 나 줘
Eric, Eric, all right,
just give me the gun.
나 믿어 달라고
총 좀 치워
You can believe me.
Put the gun down.
그총 나한테 줘
Just give me the gun.
어서! 어서!
총 달라고, 친구야!
Come on! Come on!
Give me the gun, man!
문 열어!
Open the door!
계속 시간 끌어
_
미안해
I'm sorry.
그녀가 죽을 줄은
정말 몰랐어
I never thought she'd die.
뭐?
What?
에릭, 그만 됐거든!
Eric, it's okay!
안돼!
No!
여기저기 사람들하고
전부 통화했어
I just got off the phone
with a whole host of folks.
에릭이 선교갔을 때 대한 걸
내가 맞춰본 바로는
From what I can piece together,
when Eric was on his mission,
에릭이 14살 짜리
말라위 여자애와 같이 자서
he slept with
a 14-year-old Malawian girl
임신을 시켰다는군
and got her pregnant.
여자애를
낙태하는데 데려갔는데..
He took her to get
an abortion...
그 나라에서는 불법이야..
illegal in that country...
수술 중에 죽었고
에릭은 아무한테도 말을 안했지
and she died in the process,
and he never told anyone.
우리쪽에서도 아무도
확인 못했지. 당신도 그렇고
And no one on our end
caught it, including you.
아니, 나한테
뭐라하면 안되지
No, don't pin this on me.
그앤 여기 오기 전에
He was tested, polygraphed,
시험이나 거짓말 탐지기
조사도 다 받았다고
researched,
and vetted before he got here.
당신 직접 모집했잖아
You yourself recruited him.
내가 널 보증했지
I vouched for you.
시카고 이후로 널
해고하려고 했었다고
They were gonna fire you
after Chicago.
네가 집중을
못 한다고 했었지
They said
you had lost focus.
이제 나도 알겠네
Now I see they were right.
내가 왜 아직 여깄는지
모르겠네
I don't know
why I'm still here.
아무도 날 좋아하지도 않고
제대로 하는 것도 없고
Nobody likes me.
I suck at everything.
순전히 부모님 덕분에
들어온 건데
I only got in
'cause of my parents.
너희 부모님?
Your parents?
둘다 요원이시거든
They're both agents.
입학시험도
겨우 통과했어
I barely passed
my entrance exams.
나 집어 넣으시려고
두분 연줄도 이용하셨지
They had to pull major strings
to just get me in,
어떻게 됐나 보라고
and look what happened.
에릭이 숨기던게 뭐던지
Whatever Eric was hiding,
아무도 몰랐던거야
FBI 조차도
no one knew about it,
not even the FBI.
한번 생각해봐
그런 비밀을
Just imagine if he'd
actually become an agent
가진 녀석이
실제 요원이 됐어봐
with that secret
hanging over him.
그 비밀을 지키려고
무슨 짓을 했을 지 누가 알겠어?
Who knows what he would have
done to keep it safe?
비밀이 이제 드러난거지
His secret's out now.
그찮아
우리 전부 말이야
You know,
all of ours are.
그게 어려운 거였는데
이제 다 지났잖아
That was the hard part,
but now it's over.
너희들 왜 이렇게
나한테 잘해주는거야?
Why are you
being so nice to me?
난 너희한테
병신같이 굴었는데
I've only been a jerk
to you.
그거야..
Because...
무시당하는게
어떤 기분인지 알거든
I know what it feels like
to be discounted.
그래서 나도 뭔가를
해보기로 결심한거야
That's why I decided to do
something about it.
옳소, 옳소
Hear, hear.
오늘 일어난 일에
가슴이 아픕니다
What happened today
was heartbreaking.
비극이죠
It was tragic.
하지만 상기시켜주는 것도 있죠
But it was also a reminder.
에릭 패커가 우리에게 많은 것을
보여줬다는데 믿어 의심치 않습니다만
I have no doubt Eric Packer
had much to offer us,
그는 자기 자신의 진실을
마주할 수 없었습니다
but he could not face
the truth about himself.
한명의 요원으로서
가장 중요한 일이죠
As an agent,
that's the most important thing.
여러분이 자신에게
솔직할 수 없다면
If you cannot be honest
with yourself,
어찌 다른 이들에게서
진실을 구할 수 있을까요?
how can you get the truth
out of anyone else?
그리고 여기에서
가장 두려운 것은
And the scariest part
about all of this
여기서부터가
더 힘든 것이라는 겁니다
is that it only gets harder
from here.
그러니 오늘 밤
부탁하건데
So tonight, please, please,
여러분이 인생에서 또 앞으로
무엇을 원하는 지 생각해 보세요
think about what you want
for your life, for your future.
또 그 이상으로
자신이 누구인지
More than that,
think about who you are
왜 여기 있는지 생각해 보세요
and why you're here.
감사합니다
Thank you.
하스 군?
Mr. Haas?
부원장님이 자네
남아있으라고 하시네
The Assistant Director
wants you to stay behind.
케일럽이 떠났네
Caleb's gone.
49명 남았네
49 more to go.
누구야?
Who is it?
나도 같은 질문을
해야하나?
I should ask you
the same thing.
니마 야? 미아 야?
Is it Nimah or "Mean-ah"?
멍청하긴
Stupid.
음..
Um...
솔직히, 어..
어떻게 해야하나
honestly, I would, uh,
take either one
네가 나 커피 한잔
대접하게 해주면..
if you'd let me make you
a cup of coffee...
다시 제대로 시작해
볼 수 있을 거 같은데
maybe get back
on the right foot?
바로 나갈게
I'll be right out.
어, 아, 그래
Uh, oh, great.
난.. 난..
난 밖에 있지, 음..
I'll... I'll...
I'll be out here, um...
이번엔 누구 차례지?
You or me this time?
미란다가 나랬어
Miranda said me.
그래
Okay.
이제부터는
계속 오른쪽이야
Always to the right
from now on.
부원장님
Assistant Director.
부원장님!
Assistant Director!
지메네즈 요원이
밖에서 기다리세요
Agent Jimenez
is waiting for you outside.
제한된 폭발이
두번 있었죠
Controlled explosions,
seconds apart.
선로 아래로
여러 단계에요
Multiple levels
beneath the tracks.
CIA 가 맞다면은, 우크라이나
국수주의자들이 연관됐고요
If you believe the CIA, it's
tied to Ukrainian nationalists.
국토안보부에서는
IS 라고 합니다
Homeland security
says ISIS.
우리 애기는?
How about our girl?
이제 막 상황을
맞춰보고 있네
She's starting to piece it
together.
내가 끼어들어야겠군
Maybe I should step in.
사관학교에서 그애와
그런 일이 있었는데
You really think
that's such a good idea
그래도 괜찮으시겠어?
after what happened
between you two at the Academy?
그렇다면, 잘 지켜봐
조금만 더 두고보지
All right, keep at her.
Just a little while longer.
답이 나오겠지
We'll get our answer.
그러지
All right.
좋았어
Okay.
무슨 일이에요?
제가 무슨..
What's going on?
Do you think...
제가 이일에
관련됐다고 보세요?
do you think I had
something to do with this?
그렇게 생각하시면..
Because if you do, I...
그만해도 되네
패리쉬 요원
You can stop now,
Agent Parrish.
네가 한거 아니까
We know it's you.
말도 안되요
That's ridiculous.
네가 주변 경계였으면
몇 블럭 밖에 있었어야지
If you were on perimeter detail,
you'd be blocks away,
폭발 현장에서
90미터가 아니라
not 100 yards
from the blast.
몸에 상처 하나 없는 것도
불가능하지
There's not a scratch on you,
which is impossible,
넌 폭발 후에
우리가 널 찾은 곳에
unless you placed yourself
where we found you
자릴 잡았지
그게 네가 한 짓이지
after the explosion,
which I believe that you did.
그리고 자네 총을
검사했거든
And we checked your gun.
최근에 3발의 총알이
발사됐고
It was fired recently,
three bullets,
기관에는 그런 기록이
전혀 없더군
and there's nothing on file
with the Bureau,
우리가 총알 못 찾길
빌어야 할 거야
so you better pray
that we don't find them.
영상 들어옵니다!
Video feed is live!
어디서 찾는 다고요?
Find them where?
네 아파트
At your apartment.
부셔
Break it down.
진입한다!
We're in!
FBI! FBI!
이쪽에 C4 폭탄이야!
There's C-4 over here!
폭탄 처리반 불러!
Get the bomb squad!
청사진 발견
I've got blueprints.
이거 보이십니까?
Sir!
Did you see this?
그랜드센트럴역입니다!
It's Grand Central!
누가 쓰러져 있습니다
Sir, we've got one down.
살았나? 죽었나?
Alive or dead?
부쓰 요원? 부쓰 요원?
Agent Booth? Agent Booth?
요원 사망!
Agent down!
오, 이런
Oh, my God.
어제 내 심문 과정에서
사실을 전부 말하진 않았어요
I didn't tell the whole truth
in my interview yesterday.
어머니가 아버지를
쏜게 아니에요
My mother
didn't shoot my father.
제가 쐈죠
I did.
저희 아버지예요
This is my father.
제가 알았던 분은
The man that I knew
단순하고 소박하게 사셨죠
had a simple, small life,
공장에서 단순하고
간단한 일을 하셨고요
worked a simple, small job
at a factory,
휴가도 한번 안가시고요
never took a vacation,
말도 많지 않으셨고요
never said too much.
그런 분이 특수라뇨
The kind of man
that isn't special.
분명 특수 요원이
아니셨을 거예요
He's definitely
no special agent.
이건 어디서 찾았지?
Where did you find this?
그날 밤요
That night.
어머니는 절 뭄바이 외가서
지내라고 보내셨죠
My mother sent me to Mumbai
to live with her family.
내가 널 지켜주마
I'll protect you.
10년 동안
저 혼자만 간직했죠
For 10 years,
I kept that with me.
이게 뭔지 생각을
안 할 수가 없었어요
Never stopped thinking
about it.
전혀 말이 안 되잖아요
Never made sense of it.
이제 여기까지 왔군
Now you're here.
제가 여기 온건
어머니도 모르세요
My mother
doesn't even know I'm here.
거짓말 했죠
I lied.
모두에게 거짓말 했어요
I lied to everyone.
하지만
전 진실을 알아야겠어요
But I need
to know the truth.
그분..
That man...
내가 알던 그분이 아니라면
누구였던 거죠?
if he wasn't who I knew,
who was he?
좋은 분이셨나요?
Was he good?
나쁜 분인가요?
Was he bad?
둘 다 인가요?
Was he both?
그래, 내가 좀
알아보도록 하지
Well, I can look into it
for you,
하지만, 음, 나온게
네가 좋아하리란 보장은 없어
but, um, I'm not sure
you'll like what I find.
그래도 알아야겠어요
I still need to know.
제가 위장근무에
자원했을 때는요
When I volunteer
to go undercover,
사관학교에 와서
비행기 옆자리에 앉아있던
I don't expect the Academy,
getting close to some trainee,
여자 훈련병하고
가까워지고는
sitting next to her
on a plane,
그애 서류로 그런 심문을
하게 될 줄은 몰랐거든요?
taking her file
for that interview?
그게..
It's
기분이 이상해지네요
it's starting
to feel weird.
그냥 그애랑 가까이 지내라고
알았지?
Just stay close to her,
okay?
그애가 뭘 하는지 무슨 말을
하는지 나한테 보고해
Tell me what she does,
what she says.
이거 엿같거든요
오코너 요원님
This is screwed up,
O'Connor.
부원장님이 실제로
승인한 거 맞아요?
The Assistant Director
actually approve all this?
내가 네 상관이야
부쓰 요원
I'm still your superior,
Agent Booth.
명령체계에
의문을 품지 말도록
Don't question
the chain of command.
그리고, 그애랑 또
자면 안돼
And don't sleep
with her again.
알렉산드라 패리쉬
넌 묵비권을 행사할 권리가 있으며
Alexandra Parrish, you have
the right to remain silent.
- 지금부터 하는 말은..
- 예?
- Anything you say...
- What?
..법원에서 불리하게
적용될 수 있다
...can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
뭘로 저를
체포하시는 거에요?!
What are you
arresting me for?!
어디로 데려가시는 거에요?!
Where are you taking me?!
권리가 있다고요
아시잖아요!
I have rights,
you know!
제발 누가
얘기 좀 해주세요
Will someone please
just talk to me?
제발 얘기 좀..
Just tell me...
오, 다행이네요
오셨군요
Liam, thank God
you're here.
저를 체포하는데
무슨 일인지 말도 안해줘요
They've arrested me, and
they won't even tell me why.
저기, 911 이후로
미국 영토에서 일어난
Well, how about
for what we believe
가장 충격적인
테러 공격 때문이라고
to be the most devastating
terrorist attack
보고있는데 어떤가?
on American soil
since 9/11?
부쓰 요원 시신에서
발견된 총알
The bullet
found in Agent Booth's body
자네 총에서
발사된 것과 일치하네
matches one fired
from your gun.
그것도 오늘 네가 빼앗은
다른 모든 피해자들 목록에 추가할 거야
So add that to the list of all
the other lives you took today.
리암, 저 아시잖아요
Liam, you know me.
전 어떤 테러 조직에도
연관되어 있지 않고
I have no ties
to any terrorist groups
이 나라에 대한
불만 사항도 없어요
or any grievances
against this country.
제가 이런 짓을 하거나
부쓰 요원을 쏠만한
What possible reason could I
have to do something like this
이유가 있기나 한가요?
or to shoot Agent Booth?
어쩌면, 그가 널 지켜보니까
넌 방어를 해야했나보지
Well, maybe he was onto you,
and you had to defend yourself.
아님 어쩌면 네가
그의 진실을 알아버렸던지
Or maybe you found out
the truth about him,
네가 네 아버지의 대한
진실을 알아버린 것 처럼 말야
just like you found out
the truth about your father,
넌 그게 맘에 안들었고
and you didn't like it.
진실이요?
무슨 진실이요?
The truth?
What truth?
전 쏘지..
전 쏘지 않았어요
I didn't...
I didn't shoot him.
제가 그런게 아니라고요!
I didn't do any of this!
다른 사람들은
보기나 하셨나요?
Have you even looked
at anyone else?
다른 사람들하고
얘기라도 해보셨냐고요?
Have you even talked
to anyone else?
리암, 제발 사람들
좀 말려주세요
Liam, please don't let them
do this to me.
- 제발요
- 내 눈앞에서 치워주게
- Please...
- Get her out of my sight.
가지
Let's go.
리암!
Liam!
실수하는 거야
알잖아
This is a mistake,
you know.
그만 울어
패리쉬 요원
Stop crying, Agent Parrish.
오, 세상에, 부원장님!
뭐하시는 거에요?
Oh, my God. Miranda!
What are you doing here?
넌 여기서 빼내는 거지
We have to get you
out of here.
우리 둘다
네가 테러리스트 아닌 거 알잖아
We both know
you're no terrorist.
이건 너를 노리고 일어났어
This is being pinned
on you
그 사이 진짜 범인은
빠져나가겠지
while the real perpetrator
gets away.
- 그치만 왜요?
- 나도 몰라
- But why?
- I don't know.
하지만, 너만이
바로 잡을 수 있어
But only you can fix it.
콴티코 운동장에 있던건
너였잖아
You were on the ground
at Quantico.
난 책상에나 있었지
I was behind a desk.
순간 순간을 모두
되돌아 봐야해
You have to think back
on every moment,
네가 배운데로
모두를 조사해
research everyone,
like you were taught.
하지만 어떻게요?
전 감옥에 갈텐데
But how?
I'll be in jail.
네가 감옥에
발을 들여놓으면
The moment
you set foot in there,
살아서는 절대 못 나와
you're never
getting out alive.
네 좌석 밑에
Under your seat.
좌석 밑!
Your seat!
여기
여기 열쇠
Here.
Here's a key.
오코너 요원!
Agent O'Connor!
밴 운전사가요
The driver of the van,
계단에서 의식을 잃고
쓰러져 있었습니다
they found him unconscious
in the stairwell.
밴 세워
밴 세우라고!
Stop the van.
Stop the van!
밴 세워!
Stop the van.
모든 요원에 전한다..
10-39가 진행 중이다
Calling all units...
10-39 in progress.
오, 이런
어떻게 하시려고요?
Oh, my God.
What are you gonna do?
따돌려 봐야지
I'm gonna try
to lose them.
놈들이 도주 중이다!
They're breaking away!
모두에게.. 10-59
Calling all... 10-59.
죄수 호송 차량이
Prisoner escort commandeered
신원 미상인 혹은 조직에
의해 탈취되었다
by an unidentified party
or parties.
주의하여 접근하라
Proceed with caution.
사방을 막아!
I'm gonna box them in!
꽉 잡아!
따돌릴 거니까!
Hold on!
I'm gonna try to lose them!
악!
Aah!
도망쳐!
Run!
♪ Cheated and lied ♪
♪ Broken so bad ♪
♪ You made a vow ♪
♪ Never get mad ♪
♪ You play the game ♪
♪ Though it's unfair ♪
♪ They're all the same ♪
죄수가 사라졌다!
- ♪ Who can compare? ♪
- She's gone! She's gone!
♪ First you get hurt,
then you feel sorry ♪
♪ Flying like a cannonball ♪
♪ Falling to the earth ♪
♪ Heavy as a feather
when you hit the dirt ♪
♪ How am I the lucky one? ♪
♪ I do not deserve ♪
♪ To wait around forever
when you were there first ♪
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com